http://superflygallery.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At Hokipoker, accessible from http://167.71.201.117/, one of our main
priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document
contains types of information that is collected and recorded by
Hokipoker and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is
valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that
they shared and/or collect in Hokipoker. This policy is not applicable
to any information collected offline or via channels other than this
website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.
Information we collect
The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the
reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at
the point we ask you to provide your personal information.
If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information
about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents
of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other
information you may choose to provide.
When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact
information, including items such as name, company name, address, email
address, and telephone number.
How we use your information
We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:
Provide, operate, and maintain our websteImprove, personalize, and expand our websteUnderstand and analyze how you use our websteDevelop new products, services, features, and functionalityCommunicate with you, either directly or through one of our
partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates
and other information relating to the webste, and for marketing and
promotional purposesSend you emailsFind and prevent fraud
Log Files
Hokipoker follows a standard procedure of using log files. These
files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do
this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information
collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser
type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp,
referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not
linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose
of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site,
tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic
information. Our Privacy Policy was created with the help of the Privacy Policy Generator and the Privacy Policy Template.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Like any other website, Hokipoker uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are
used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages
on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is
used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page
content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.
Advertising Partners Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Hokipoker.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies,
JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective
advertisements and links that appear on Hokipoker, which are sent
directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address
when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the
effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the
advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that Hokipoker has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Party Privacy Policies
Hokipoker’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or
websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy
Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information.
It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of
certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies
and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser
options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with
specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective
websites. What Are Cookies?
CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)
Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:
Request that a business that collects a consumer’s personal data
disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a
business has collected about consumers.
Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.
Request that a business that sells a consumer’s personal data, not sell the consumer’s personal data.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you
would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.
GDPR Data Protection Rights
We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:
The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your
personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.
The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we
correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the
right to request that we complete the information you believe is
incomplete.
The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that
we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain
conditions.
The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to
our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we
transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or
directly to you, under certain conditions.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you
would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.
Children’s Information
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while
using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe,
participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
Hokipoker does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable
Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your
child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly
encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts
to promptly remove such information from our records.
© Copyright 2020, IDNPLAY By Hokipoker with IDN POKER ONLINE Dan DOMINO QQ. Hak Cipta Dilindungi.
Beranda
Daftar
Login
Live Chat
